ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Splendor Form Brassiere Inc., 1986 (Box 100, Folder 131)
- Spintex Corporation, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 132)
  Cumberland, RI
- Spudland Marketing, Inc., 1986 (Box 100, Folder 133)
- Spunfibers, Inc., 1984 (Box 100, Folder 134)
  Fieldale, VA; Article Photocopy
- Summer Paradise Inc., 1984 (Box 100, Folder 135)
- Sunburst Fashions Ltd., 1984 (Box 100, Folder 136)
- Suntek Industries, Inc., 1985 (Box 100, Folder 137)
- Sunshine Laundry, Inc., 1986 (Box 100, Folder 138)
- Stablex South Carolina, Inc., 1984 (Box 100, Folder 139)
- Stacy Industries, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 140)
- Stallings Tire & Battery Service, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 141)
- Star Linen Co., 1985 (Box 100, Folder 142)
- Stanaland, Inc., 1986 (Box 100, Folder 143)
- Star Paper Tube, Inc., 1966-1984 (Box 100, Folder 144)
- Status Tables, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 145)
- Stratojac, Inc. [Folder 1 of 2], 1964-1989 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Stratojac, Inc. [Folder 2 of 2], 1964-1989 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Style Craft Corporation, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Styled Hats Co., Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Susquehanna Textile Co. Ltd., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Stuffco International, Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Stoughton Elastic Web Co., Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Sun Chemical Corporation, 1968-1987 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Sunrise Screen Textile Corporation, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  Farmingdale, NY
- Swan Finishing Co., Inc., 1974-1983 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Sweetwater Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1965-1985 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Symbolic Displays, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Tamal Company, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- TMG Corporation, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Tams Mills Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Tale Lord Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1977-1984 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Tenax Corporation, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- Tennken Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Tarmak Enterprises, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- Troutman Industries, Inc., 1967-1986 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Tucker Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- Tuftex Carpet Mills, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- Tru-Fit Fashions Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- Tropico Hats Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Trio Plating Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- Les Tricots Smart, Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Scancelli Prints, Inc., 1980 (Box 101, Folder 27)
  E. Rutherford, NJ
- Treco, Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- Transfer Fashion Print, Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- Transco Group, Inc., 1980-1986 (Box 101, Folder 30)
- Town & Country Transportation of Lincoln, Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 31)
  Warren, RI
- Totes, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 32)
- Torrent Corporation, 1978-1985 (Box 101, Folder 33)
  Citronelle, AL
- Topps & Trowsers Inc., 1973-1984 (Box 101, Folder 34)
- Tompkins Fabrics, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 35)
- Toby Industries Limited, 1978-1984 (Box 101, Folder 36)
- Timber Lake, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 37)
- Tiffany Leather Co., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 38)
- Tidwell Industries, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 39)
- Three Printers, Inc., 1970-1985 (Box 101, Folder 40)
- Thrasher's, Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 41)
- Thomasville Furniture Industries, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 42)
- Thielex Plastics Corporation, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 43)
  Plainfield, NJ
- Thermco Products Corporation, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 44)
- Turner's Dairy, Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 45)
- Textile Printing & Finishing Co., Inc., 1966-1984 (Box 101, Folder 46)
  Article Photocopies Included; Lebanon, PA
- Textile Converters, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 47)
  Hermitage, TN
- Texstyle Creators Ltd., Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 48)
- Joseph Teshon, Inc., 1982 (Box 101, Folder 49)
- Usdan Kolmes Industries, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 50)
- Patricia Underwood, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 51)
- URO Fabrics, Ltd., 1983-1985 (Box 101, Folder 52)
- U.S. Finishing Co., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 53)
- Union Camp Corporation. General Labor [Folder 1 of 2], 1972-1993 (Box 101, Folder 54)
  Chase Packaging, Subsidiary
- Union Camp Corporation. General Labor [Folder 2 of 2], 1972-1993 (Box 101, Folder 55)
- United Cloth Co., Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 101, Folder 56)
  See also: A. Sheftel & Co.; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included
- Unitas National Bank, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 57)
- United Merchants & Manufacturers, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 101, Folder 58)
  Homestead Manufacturing Co.; Augusta, GA; Newspaper Clipping and Photocopy Included
- Warrenton Refining Co., Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 59)
- H. Warshow & Sons, Inc., 1969-1982 (Box 101, Folder 60)
  Milton, PA
- Waumbec Mills, Inc., 1972-1984 (Box 101, Folder 61)
- Waveline, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 101, Folder 62)
- John Weitz, Inc., 1969-1984 (Box 101, Folder 63)
- Wellfleet Fabric Corporation, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 64)
- West Coast Lining Co., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 65)
- West Virginia Plastics Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 66)
- Westmills Canada Ltd., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 67)
- Westville Homes Corporation, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 68)
  Subsidiary Of Amoskeag Co.
- White Stag Manufacturing Co., 1961-1984 (Box 101, Folder 69)
- Whitlock Combing Co., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 70)
- Whittall & Javits Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 101, Folder 71)
- Wibbies, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 72)
- Wilker Brothers Co., Inc., 1957-1985 (Box 101, Folder 73)
- Wilmington Finishing Co., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 74)
- Wilshire Bedding Co., Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 75)
- Wilson Shirt Co., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 76)
- Winay, Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 77)
  Passaic, NJ
- Winebarger Corporation, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 78)
- Winona Knitting Mills, Inc., 1973-1984 (Box 101, Folder 79)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy; Winona, MN
- Winston Mills, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 101, Folder 80)
- Valley Screen Printing Co., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 81)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy Included; Lebanon, PA
- Valley View Nursing Home, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 82)
- Vander Dyeing & Finishing Corporation, 1984-1985 (Box 101, Folder 83)
- Varela Slacks Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 84)
- Vaughan Furniture Co., Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 85)
- Vee-go Industries Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 86)
  Athens, AL
- Vegetable Juices Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 87)
- Vernon Plastics Corporation, 1971-1985 (Box 101, Folder 88)
- Vertical Apparel Planning, Inc., 1985 (Box 101, Folder 89)
- Victor Electric Wire & Cable Corporation, 1978-1984 (Box 101, Folder 90)
- Virginia Maid Hosiery Mills, Inc., 1969-1985 (Box 101, Folder 91)
- Viviano Macaroni Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 92)
  Schenectady, NY
- Vogue Shoes, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box 101, Folder 93)
- Vulcan Corporation, 1979-1983 (Box 101, Folder 94)
  Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included; 1979 Annual Report Included
- Walker-Gordon Laboratory Co., Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 95)
- SC Walker Manufacturing Co. Ltd. (Box 101, Folder 96)
- Ware Novelty Spinners, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 97)
- Ware Shoals Dyeing & Finishing Corporation, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 98)
- Jack Winter, Inc., 1968-1985 (Box 101, Folder 99)
- Winwood Sportswear, Inc., 1986 (Box 101, Folder 100)
- Wollip Corporation, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 101)
- Woodstream Corporation, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 102)
- Woolfolk Manufacturing Corporation, 1967-1984 (Box 101, Folder 103)
- Worcester Textile Co., 1973-1985 (Box 101, Folder 104)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; Centerdale, RI
- Worker International, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 105)
- Wyandotte Industries Corporation [Folder 1 of 2], 1980-1984 (Box 101, Folder 106)
  See also: First Hartford Corporation
- Wyandotte Industries Corporation [Folder 2 of 2], 1980-1984 (Box 101, Folder 107)
- X-Tyal International Corporation, 1981-1986 (Box 101, Folder 108)
- Yale Cordage Inc., 1980-1986 (Box 101, Folder 109)
- Zada Specialty Corporation, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 110)
- Abraham Zion Corporation, 1981-1986 (Box 101, Folder 111)
- Zipper Cord, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 112)
- Zipper Weaving, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 113)
- Zody's, 1984-1986 (Box 101, Folder 114)